module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'how long was the first thanksgiving celebration?', 
    a: '2 hours',
    b: 'a week',
    c: 'a month',
    d: '3 days',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'the woman behind which song is also responsible for Thanksgiving’s recognition?', 
    a: 'Twinkle Twinkle Little Star',
    b: 'Hokey Pokey',
    c: 'Mary Had a Little Lamb',
    d: 'Old Macdonald',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was missing from the first \'s Thanksgiving Day Parade? ', 
    a: 'Turkey',
    b: 'The crowd',
    c: 'Alcohol',
    d: 'Balloons',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'A Thanksgiving mix-up inspired what?', 
    a: 'Mashed Potatoes',
    b: 'Pumpkin Pie',
    c: 'TV Dinners',
    d: 'Rumchatas',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Approximately how many turkeys are cooked for Thanksgiving each year?', 
    a: '20 million',
    b: '46 Million',
    c: '3 Billion',
    d: '800,000',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many places in the US are named ‘turkey’?', 
    a: 'none',
    b: '2',
    c: '4',
    d: '10',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Greek Goddess of Corn is?', 
    a: 'Starchy',
    b: 'Demeter',
    c: 'Cleopatra',
    d: 'Cornholia',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The term "Cornucopia" means what?', 
    a: 'corn land',
    b: 'city of corn',
    c: 'starchy’s house',
    d: 'horn of plenty',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year did the first Macy\'s Thanksgiving parade take place', 
    a: '1919',
    b: '1905',
    c: '1928',
    d: '1924',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which booze did the pilgrims take with them on their voyage?', 
    a: 'rum',
    b: 'beer',
    c: 'vodka',
    d: 'whisky',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];